"Will you go on the record?"
She Said is a drama, history film directed by Maria Schrader.
New York Times reporters Megan Twohey and Jodi Kantor break one of the most important stories in a generation — a story that
helped launch the #MeToo movement and shattered decades of silence around the subject of sexual assault in Hollywood.
Megan Twohey, played by Carey Mulligan.
Jodi Kantor, played by Zoe Kazan.
Rebecca Corbett, played by Patricia Clarkson.
Dean Baquet, played by Andre Braugher.
Young Laura, played by Lola Petticrew.
Irish Film Crew Woman, played by Katherine Laheen.
She Said is a 2022 American drama film directed by Maria Schrader and written by Rebecca
Lenkiewicz, based on the 2019 book by reporters Jodi Kantor and Megan Twohey.
The film stars Carey Mulligan and Zoe Kazan as Twohey and Kantor, respectively, and follows their New York Times
investigation that exposed Harvey Weinstein's history of abuse and sexual misconduct against women.
The film also stars Patricia Clarkson, Jennifer Ehle, Samantha Morton, and
Andre Braugher, in his final film role before his death in 2023.
Ashley Judd appears as herself.
The book was optioned in 2018, and the film was announced in 2021 as a
co-production between Annapurna Pictures and Plan B Entertainment.
Filming took place in New York with cinematographer Natasha Braier.
During post-production, editing was completed by Hansjörg
Weißbrich and the score was composed by Nicholas Britell.
She Said had its world premiere at the 60th New York Film Festival on October 13, 2022, and
was released in the United States on November 18, 2022, by Universal Pictures.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics, who praised
the screenplay and the performances of Kazan and Mulligan.
It was also named one of the best films of 2022 by the American Film Institute.
However, it was a box-office bomb, grossing $13.9 million
against a production budget of $32 million.
The film was nominated for Best Actress in a Supporting Role for Mulligan and Best
Adapted Screenplay for Lenkiewicz at the 76th British Academy Film Awards.
It also earned Mulligan a Golden Globe Award nomination and
Lenkiewicz a Critics' Choice Award nomination.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, journalism,
biography, sexual violence, sexual harassment.
The tone is emotional.